shop2market.com 2019-04-20

# Privacy policy - AdCurve

This privacy policy is applicable to the [ **AdCurve.com**](http://adcurve.com/) website and application, and any other products or services (collectively, ‘Services’), of Shop2market BV. We are registered in The Netherlands under company number 32120991. Our office is located at De Strubbenweg 7, 1327GA Almere. In circumstances where we are a data controller, the data controller is Shop2market BV (“we”/”Shop2market BV”/”AdCurve”).

AdCurve is a software company that engineers cloud-based digital marketing solutions and predictive media optimization technology.

As such, we collect, process and analyze data from various sources, produce statistical information and identify trends in order to enable our customers to manage, optimize and analyze their digital marketing activities across multiple advertising channels and devices. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy principles and practices applied by AdCurve in the course of providing services to its customers and from individuals visiting our website.

AdCurve, at all times, is committed to and actively seeks to protect and respect your privacy. This is of critical important to us.

This policy addresses and defines the universal policy and specific protocols that AdCurve has in place for the management and processing of all personal data including (but not limited to) that which is:

  * Generated and collected on our websites,
  * Generated and collected through our customers sites,
  * Generated and handled internally at AdCurve.

We protect your privacy and our objectives are to be transparent about how we process your personal data.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information about the following:

  * What information we may collect about you;
  * How we will use information we collect about you;
  * Whether we will disclose your details to anyone else; and
  * Your choices and rights regarding the personal information you have provided to us.

Any concerns or comments about this policy and questions about deleting or correcting your personal data should directed to our support team at [privacy@AdCurve.com](mailto:privacy@adcurve.com)

Our Website may contain hyperlinks to services owned and operated by third parties. These third party services may have their own privacy policies and we recommend that you review them.  We do not accept any responsibility or liability for the privacy practices of such third party services and your use of these is at your own risk.

### Our Services

AdCurve services allow customers to manage, optimize and analyze their digital marketing activities across multiple advertising channels and devices. As such, AdCurve does not have a direct relationship with users who visit or otherwise engage customer websites or are exposed to customer’s advertisements that are managed using our services.

AdCurve may collect and use information related to users as part of the provision of the AdCurve services to our customers.

As a rule of thumb, the information collected by AdCurve is typically used to identify trends and optimize overall advertising activities of our customers. As such, this information is un-identifiable, and we do not know, nor will we attempt to know the identity of Users.

AdCurve requires its customers to acknowledge this Privacy Policy in order to promote transparency of our privacy practices to users.

###   
Fundamental principles

  * We do not process personal data unless we need it to deliver our products and services or to run our company efficiently.
  * We don’t share your personal information (without your consent) with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products or services or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our products or services.
  * We do use cookies and other similar tools to help us collect and store information about you and other users of our products and services.

### The type of information we collect from you

We may collect and process the following information:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on sites we operate. This includes information provided at the time of log in to use our site, subscribing to our service, requesting further services (including news) participating in surveys or promotions. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our sites or our products and services.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders. billing purposes, to deliver and improve our products and services or otherwise.
  * We may collect information about your computer, including without limitation, language preference, referring site, operating system and browser type. Statistical data about website users’ browsing actions and patterns does not identify any individual. This statistical data provides us with information regarding how many users visit a specific page on which our products and services are installed, how long they stay on that page, the type of content on that page, which hyperlinks (if any) they “click” on and how they generally engage with that page. This information is generally non-identifying, but if we combine it with you as a specific and identifiable person, we will treat it as personal information.
  * AdCurve also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or device characteristics. 

### We use anonymized and aggregated information

When it comes to delivering our products and services, our mission is to improve websites and empower them to deliver better products to their customers. We do this by analysing a user’s entire journey on a website for customers. What we do requires us to collect data of users on websites. We anonymise user data collected on sites where our products and services are installed and use it (typically in an aggregated form) to determine the customer journey, publish reports and improve our products and services.

### We share your personal information in limited circumstances

  * AdCurve discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that: (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AdCurve’s behalf or to provide products and services on behalf of AdCurve; and (ii) comply with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country and you consent to the transfer of such information to them.
  * AdCurve will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.
  * Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations, as described above, AdCurve discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when AdCurve believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AdCurve, third parties or the public at large (this includes without limitation exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.)
  * If you are a registered user of a AdCurve website and have supplied your email address, AdCurve may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with AdCurve and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. AdCurve takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

###   
Yes we do use tracking pixels and cookies. Here is how and why and what you can do if you do not want the AdCurve cookies:

In order to obtain information, we may use Tracking Pixels and Cookies.

A tracking pixel is a piece of code embedded on a web page of customer’s website that collects information about users’ engagement on that web page. The tracking pixel can be provided either by the advertising channels, affiliate networks or by AdCurve. The Tracking Pixel may include a command to create cookies.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AdCurve uses cookies to help AdCurve identify and track users on sites operated by AdCurve and sites on which AdCurve’s products and services are installed.

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies or choose to disable Cookies by clicking on the disable cookies icon. If you find it difficult to change the setting on your browser please go to [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) where you will find information on how to do this on a wide variety of browsers. Please be aware however, that if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

#### The cookies used by AdCurve are:

Shop2market is a web analytics tool making use of shop side cookies to determine the added value of online advertisements. Webshops use the aggregated insights to optimize their online campaigns. 

All the cookies we create in performing the Services are set from the merchant’s domain and are first-party cookies:

**Name** | **Expiration time** | **Description**  
---|---|---  
__s2m_order_page_sid_{shop_id} | session | Cart cookie, used for cart freeze functionality  
__s2m_vals_{shop_id} | 10 years | This cookie is used to: 

– collect all assists within the tracking period  
– track visitors  
– this cookie contains a timestamp which is updated on every visit.  
  
__s2m_sid_{shop_id} | session | Session id 

This session cookie together with stid is used to:  
– distinct visits from views  
– to track sessions  
  
__s2m_stid_{shop_id} | session | This cookie contains a timestamp which is updated on every view  
__s2m_pid_{shop_id} | session | Hash from url params to prevent back button visits, and page refresh visits  
optin | 10 years | Used by Adcurve’s cookie popup to store user’s preferences  
  
#### Functional platform cookies by AdCurve:

**Name** | **Expiration time** | **Description**  
---|---|---  
_capuchin_session | Session or 30 days | Login session id for application  
x-s2m-auth | 2 weeks | API token to access s2m’s APIs  
_shop2market_session | Session or 30 days | Login session id for application  
  
Furthermore a number of tools are used to perform Our Services. These parties are:

  * Intercom  – is a customer messaging platform used by to provide support adequately and swiftly to (potential) users of our services. For more information about Intercom and their privacy policy visit: https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy

  * SendGrid  – is an email delivery service used to communicate with our users regularly, to inform about important updates and send any other notification via our platform. For more information about SendGrid and their privacy policy visit: https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/

  * Google Analytics  – is used to for the purpose of analyzing the interaction of users with our websites and to continuously optimize their performance. The information collected may be device information, local storage, cookies and other techniques. For more information about Google Analytics and their privacy policy visit: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

### Consent to transfer of information

Our servers are located in Ireland. 

It is possible that your personal information may be transferred outside of the EU by any of our Partners. We recommend that you refer to their privacy policies and/or terms and conditions if you are concerned about your data being transferred outside the EU.

Where we transfer your information outside of the EU, we have agreements in place with those parties which include standard data protection clauses adopted by a data protection regulator and approved by the European Commission to ensure that appropriate safeguards are in place to protect your personal data.  If you would like to find out more about these safeguards, please let us know by writing to privacy@AdCurve.com.

### Here is what happens to your personal information if there is a business transfer:

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase a business or assets. If we purchase another entity or if another entity acquires us or all or substantially all of our assets, or assets related to the AdCurve product offering, personal information, user data, and any other information that we have collected about the users of our products and services may be disclosed to such entity as part of the due diligence process and, if we or our assets are acquired, will be transferred to such entity as one of the transferred assets. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of AdCurve may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### How do we keep personal information secure?

We maintain tight controls over all the data we collect, retaining it in firewalled and secured databases with strictly limited and controlled access rights, to ensure it is secure. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access certain features of the service, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Please do not share this password with anyone. You are solely responsible for all access to our products and services using your password.

We will undertake internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorised access to systems where we store personal data. Please remember however that unfortunately no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you subscribe to our services, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

### Your rights in relation to personal data which we process relating to you

You have the following rights over the way we process personal data relating to you, as set out in the table below.  We aim to comply without undue delay, and within one month at the latest.

To make a request, please let us know by sending an email to privacy@AdCurve.com. 

Ask for a copy of data we are processing about you and have inaccuracies corrected

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected.

We will use reasonable efforts to the extent required by law to supply, correct or delete personal information held about you on our files (and with any third parties to whom it has been disclosed to).

Object to us processing data about you

You can ask us to restrict, stop processing, or to delete your personal data if:

  * you consented to our processing the personal data, and have withdrawn that consent;
  * we no longer need to process that personal data for the reason it was collected;
  * we are processing that personal data because it is in the public interest or it is in order to pursue a legitimate interest of TT or a third party, you don’t agree with that processing, and there is no overriding legitimate interest for us to continue processing it;
  * the personal data was unlawfully processed;
  * you need the personal data to be deleted in order to comply with legal obligations;
  * the personal data is processed in relation to the offer of a service to a child.

Obtain a machine readable copy of your personal data, which you can use with another service provider

  * If we are processing data in order to perform our obligations to you, or because you consented, if that processing is carried out by automated means, we will help you to move, copy or transfer your personal data to other IT systems.
  * If you request, we will supply you with the relevant personal data in CSV format.  Where it is technically feasible, you can ask us to send this information directly to another IT system provider if you prefer. 

### Data Retention

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant service, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

### Dutch Data Protection Authority

You have the right to file a complaint with the Dutch Data Protection Authority. 

### We may make changes to this policy

Although most changes are likely to be minor, AdCurve may change its privacy and cookie policy from time to time (in AdCurve’s sole discretion). Any changes we may make to our privacy and cookie policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where it makes sense, notified to you by e-mail or in another appropriate manner.

_**This Privacy Policy was updated to be effective 25 th May 2018.**_
